Erdni Zergetaev

zergetaev@gmail.com +79962590913 Moscow

Summary

Full Stack web developer with 5.5 years of experience. Built a few successful projects from scratch and worked on huge websites with millions of users and legacy code. I understand both the technical and the product side of an online business.

Open to remote contracts and visa sponsorship proposals.

Work experience

CTO

rabota08.ru • Elista 09/2021 - Present

- Launched the MVP which gathered 500+ early clients
- Integrated APM and Error Tracking Software
- Formulated the business model with the CEO

Senior Full Stack Developer (remote)

Bonfire • San Francisco, California

05/2021 - Present

- Implemented an airdrops feature on blockchain
- Refactored parts of codebase, increased test coverage with Jest, added granural typings which allowed to fix many financial bugs
- Participated in archectural decisions such as choosing the tools for caching, background workers, etc.

Senior fullstack developer (remote)

Busbud • Montreal, Quebec

08/2019 - 05/2021

- Added support for selling train tickets, which will increase the amount of sold tickets by a magnitude
- Refactored parts of legacy codebase with TypeScript, signifcantly improved test coverage with Jest
- Made a russian version: worked with translators, designers and marketers to adapt the website to the local market, laws and partners

Stack: TypeScript, Express.js, React.js/Redux, Jest, PostgreSQL, Docker.

Principal Full Stack Developer (remote)

Vayable • San Francisco, California

05/2019 - 08/2019

- Migrated legacy codebase from Rails 3 to Rails 5
- Moved to a React.js frontend, which allowed for many QoL features and improved performance
- Added JSON API for said frontend and partners
- Significantly improved test coverage with Rspec, FactoryBot and Capybara

Full stack developer

Krypton Capital 12/2017 - 05/2019

jury.online - an escrow platform for safe investments in blockchain startups. During my tenure the project has successfully raised more than *3 million dollars* in investments.

- Developed a web dashboard for Ethereum smart contract. Worked with Solidity developers to integrate smart contracts via Metamask Browser extension.
- Developed a JSON API with accompanying Swagger documentation.

Selected Accomplishments:

I was the only developer responsible for developing the dashboard in time before the ICO, and I have succeeded, helping the project to raise more than 3 million dollars in Ethereum investments.

Tech: Ruby on Rails, PostgreSQL, Bootstrap, React.js, Web3.js, Webpack, Rspec, Capybara

buzz.im - a platform for advertising in Telegram messenger. Responsibilities:

- Optimized performance to achieve 90+ scoring on Google PageSpeed Insights
- Worked with the developers of telegram bot to integrate its capabilities into the platform
- Developed a JSON API with accompanying Swagger documentation, which is used by Vue.js frontend
- Worked with with designers on mockups for a design revamp, integrated the resulting HTML & CSS into the platform.
- Helped the marketing department with their job by improving SEO and creating helpful metrics with Metabase.

Stack: Ruby on Rails 5, MySQL, Bootstrap, StimulusJS, jQuery, Rspec, Capybara

Fullstack web developer

Freelancer 02/2016 - 12/2017

Professional Skills

- Rails
- Redux
- PostgreSQL
- Docker
- Node.js
- Bootstrap
- Next.js
- Web3

- React
- TypeScript
- Rspec
- Jauery
- GraphQL
- Stimulus.js
- Ethereum

Education

Entrepreneurship

Russian Business Leaders 2021

Russian Business Leaders is a US State Department program for young Russians engaged in business leadership positions to gain exposure to work in the US private sector.

Bachelor's degree in Information Technology

Kalmyk State University • Elista

06/2017

Graduation project, called "Processing and analysis of the results of expert evaluation of a set of alternatives aka Delphi method " had received an excellent mark and was featured on local TV.